It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your call.
Let's keep on going.
I'm not dead.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh,
oh, oh
Let's do it again You know what I mean,
baby No one can make my dream
come true Don't you feel it,
I really don't know what is Something
is testing me every day Hey,
let's go Let's fly away I know I
never wanna come back here Hey,
let's go Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules Standing up,
blowing up My dream is getting
wilder I'm not afraid, beat me,
hit me I will never
turn around Another day,
another chance You know it's
never too late If I can't do it,
so can you only without
It's my life, it's your
life Party for tomorrow,
go get what you really want I want more,
anyone more, come on, open up the door
It's my life,
it's your life Run like
a wind, jump high, yeah,
yeah I know you're strong Believe you cannot
achieve your goal Let's keep on going,
roaring It's my life, it's your life
Fighting for your eyes that I want,
but you're where it was
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate It's my life,
it's your light, shine like a star
to be good I know you're strong,
trust that you can't achieve your
best Let's keep on going out of date
You make my day every day
I don't believe it.
He saved Dressrosa just like
King Rick said he would.
Thanks to him, Dressrosa is free!
Go, Gumball Guy!
Gumball?
No, he's a lot more than that.
Hm?
Didn't you hear King
Riku's speech? Come on!
He's the pirate they call Straw Hat Loopy!
You're right here!
We love you!
Wait a second.
You saw Luffy's face in the newspaper.
This guy looks way different.
So how can we be sure it's him?
Sorry, but are you Straw
Hat Luffy? Uh, yeah.
I heard Straw Hat's a monster,
like 26 feet tall. But this guy?
He can't be more than 14 feet or so.
Does that mean he's a fake?
Hey, bouncy boy, are you legit or not?
Give it a rest.
Why are you still bouncing around?
Can't you stop that?
Viola Straw Hat.
He did it really. You're sure!
Amazing!
What a devastating blow!
There's no way he survived such a thing.
Look at the sky.
Not enough!
The damn birdcage, it's still there!
One more, then you're done.
It's time for Kuma Kuma!
Hey, what's the matter? Are you okay?
That's Jesus Burgess.
What's he doing here?
He landed!
That I had no idea he could jump that far!
Hey!
Sabo, are you there?
Come on, pick up—it looks like
Straw Hats at the end of his rope!
This is my chance!
I know
that guy!
He's
the captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's pirate group;
they call him Champ Burgess!
You've got something,
and I want it—which means you're dead!
The Gum-Gum fruit is mine!
Are you
all right?
We can't get too close!
He's still a pirate—remember,
and pirates shouldn't be trusted!
Who knows what he's gonna do next?
But how can you say that?
He beat Doflamingo if not for him,
the whole kingdom would be done for!
Yeah!
She's right!
That guy isn't going to
hurt us! I don't know!
I just can't trust him now!
Don't forget King Rick said that straw
hat Luffy would be the one to save us!
Come on!
Tell us man!
This was the battle over now or what?
What about dopamine?
what about dopamine Domingo, is he dead?
It's no good!
He's still alive!
We have to get away from town!
Those two fires aren't
done toaking it out yet!
Even downtown isn't safe, Val!
Then where the hell do we go?
The birdcage is closing in!
There's nowhere left to run!
Damn it, Bingo.
Let's go.
Sorry, but I can't help you.
Poor guy.
I don't think he can go on.
If you turn back, you'll
die along with him.
Keep running!
Let the pirate sort it out.
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
Do you recognize me?
It's Gyat!
From the tournament!
Remember?
That mysterious warrior named Lucy!
It was you!
Ha!
Ha! It's true!
For one so small, you've
got serious strength!
Doflamingo's about to strike!
Quick, what's your next move?
Is there anything I
can do to help you out?
Buy me ten minutes. Hurt.
After I use Bounce Man, I have to
wait ten minutes to recharge my Haki.
Bounce Man? Okay.
I don't know what
Doflamingo's next move is,
but I'm pretty much useless right
now, so I gotta stay away from him.
Once my Haki comes back,
I'll give him one good punch,
and that'll be the end of it.
I promise.
If I make that happen,
we're free from this mess.
Tell me,
do you really think in ten minutes you can
beat Doflamingo and get
rid of the birdcage?
Hey, answer me!
I know I can.
All right.
Ten minutes.
Can you men work with that? Yeah!
No sweat.
It'll go by faster than
the blink of an eye.
Take it easy, Lucy.
After you rest up, you can
really suck at the Doflamingo.
Let us handle the rest.
Those are all the other
competitors from the tournament.
They're the same people who
weren't willing to help you before.
Forgive us, Lucy.
We shouldn't have gotten so
distracted by the bounty on your head.
Yeah, we didn't know you'd give
Joe Flamingo a run for his money.
We're sorry.
As an apology, we'll put our
lives on the line to help you out.
Sorry if we beat him
before you get a chance.
Guess we can finally give
you a proper thank you, Mr.
Heavenly Demon.
We've got a lot to say, so
this could take a while.
He's looking for a fight, huh?
Let's get him!
All right, now's our chance.
The other half of you
follow my lead! Right!
Out! Huh?
Ah!
Too bad! I've gotcha!
What?
Not this guy again!
Hey, Sabo!
Hey, isn't that...
Yeah, he's one of the three stars.
Who is he?
The Revolutionary Army's Chief of Staff!
Yeah, I'm everything you say.
And I came here to save
my brother, Luffy. Huh?
Now, what is it you
want with him, Burgess?
He's your brother?
That's interesting.
Wonder why that ring's a bell.
I'm sure Firefist Ace said it, too.
He's our brother, as well.
Huh?
After the battle on Bonnaroo Island,
You blackbeard pirates took Ace captive,
and that ended up being the catalyst
for that terrible battle in Marineford.
Ace made his own choice, so I
won't blame you for what happened.
But I'll be watching Luffy's
back from here on out.
Don't forget that!
Do you think I care about
your little brotherly bond?
Or about you or the
Revolutionary Army's plans?
This is between me and him.
Just you and him?
I wouldn't be so sure.
This!
Bastard!
That was you?
What?
He ate it?
Hey, Luffy. Huh?
I'm sorry I can't do more.
Doflamingo's on his way over.
And I'm gonna have my hands
pretty full with this guy.
I'll be fine.
Ketz and those other dudes said
they'd buy more time for me.
The name's Ketz.
Then I can take care of Mingo, no problem.
Wow, you're the man with
the plan, aren't you?
Then leave this to me.
Sabo, Ace's fruit, you ate it.
well i couldn't give it up
could i it was our brothers
yeah good thinking that
ability's gonna be my little man
keep him safe pets my name's
guts but i got him Whee-ha-ha-ha!
Galleon Lariat!
Now burning dragon claw fist!
That's hot!
And flame Dragon King!
But I just lost?
That guy works for one
of the four emperors.
Yeah, but Sabo, that guy's
a big-shot revolutionary.
As soon as he saw the
Flame Flame Fruit's power,
he turned all of his attention to me.
I guess that means the rumors were true.
Burgess is hunting down people
who possess Devil Fruit abilities.
Hold on, Lucy.
I'm confused.
I thought you won the competition
and got the Flame Flame Fruit.
Lucy in the last round wasn't me.
I had to go somewhere, so
Sabo fought in my place.
That's a blatant violation of tournament
rules, but I suppose it all worked out.
Right, taking over your deceased
brother's ability was a noble goal indeed.
And besides,
giving you a chance to recover
and overthrow Doflamingo
is the only hope our kingdom
has left at this point.
Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
We've been wearing him down, but
he's still got so much strength.
Don't give up now.
We have to keep stalling him.
You're nothing but flies.
I could kill the lot of you with my eyes
closed if I didn't have
more important business.
Now come and face me, Straw Hat.
I'll make you regret this.
I said face me!
I think the wood wants us dead.
I can't believe we used
to light that maniac.
The birdcage wasn't enough?
Now he's gonna turn the whole
town into killer strings?
Even if we live, Triss Rosa is done for!
Forget about the buildings and run!
If we don't get clear of
downtown, we're all gonna die!
The kingdom is like a
battlefield everywhere!
We're running out of places to go!
I ain't dying because of a
bunch of stupid strings, dammit!
It's got to be safe downtown, right?
Hey, stop showing.
Back off, you're going to crush me.
I have children, watch out.
Everyone, stop right there.
Hey, why are you running this way?
Downtown is the only safe place.
No, downtown is a battlefield, man. What?
And then we're stuck.
Where the hell are we supposed to go?
Please, King Rick.
The kingdom is dying.
Can't you help us somehow?
Here goes. Armament.
Do you really think your swords can
stop the cage's movement, Sir Zoro?
It isn't something that
can simply be pushed back.
How do you know?
Rather than telling me that
can't be done, how about you try?
You want to die whining?
At the end of the day, this
is just one man's power.
So there's no reason to believe that I
can't stop it your friend speaks the truth.
Yes, let's go
You guys ready to go
Factory is see prism stone.
It won't get shredded.
So I want you bros to push it
with everything you've got Yeah!
On up!
Now, it's go time, baby!
Whatcha gonna do?
I said, whatcha gonna do?
It's on me!
Zora's pushing the birdcage, yes.
You think it could be stopped?
It's hard to say.
I'd never even really
considered it quite honestly.
In that case, let's wish him luck.
I'm just doing what the
young master would want!
Screw you!
Get out of the way!
Thank you!
You can't do this!
Kaku punk!
You stay down there!
This is the new King's Plateau!
If you're not in the Don Quixote family,
then you weren't allowed to be here!
The executives all got their asses kicked!
There is no family!
You can't keep the safest place
in the kingdom all to yourself.
Don't you get it?
All of you are condemned criminals.
The young master has
decided that the kingdom
will be rebuilt from the
ground up without you.
Barrier, barrier, pistol!
It's sucking.
Your old news, this
ain't your turf no more.
The Coliseum Fighters are here.
More to Luffy.
Hi Rudin.
Don't cheat Joe!
Oh, Commander Kiros is here, too!
Why am I able to move again? It's strange.
I was injured quite badly,
but I feel fine now.
You should make the most
of it while you can.
This is a life support procedure that
Princess Monchery has
used on all of Dressrosa.
I'm lost.
What do you mean by life support?
Details can wait.
Let's make our way to the plateau.
Go.
The center of the birdcage
is moving this way.
Let's go!
Thanks for saving us.
You're the best.
Hey, don't be lazy.
We still need help.
If any of you've got muscle,
we'll accept you with open arms.
Oh, gosh.
With open arms, you say?
Hey, where are you going?
We're not done yet.
If you don't want to come and play,
I'll just have to drag you out.
oh man no way wait a second
is it speeding up it's
gotta be we've got If we
had it bad enough already,
how are we supposed to outrun it now?
Please, King Rick, we're counting on you!
I can't keep this up!
Please, spare them!
I'm dead for it! Don't give up!
Put your backs into it!
I won't for lift!
What's up?
Push through!
I'm losing ground!
Even if it's speeding
up, you guys got this.
Keep pushing her.
Make those strings cry.
Okay, push!
Push!
All right, this is our
chance to show off. Yeah!
I can't find you, Straw Hat.
Can't anybody help us?
We're on our own!
We just gotta keep running for it!
Only three minutes remain until
the birdcage reaches downtown,
at which point the citizens of
Dressrosa will be wiped out completely.
You've gotta be kidding!
We're never gonna make it at this rate!
Four minutes remain until
Luffy can use his Haki again.
Therefore,
the other fighters in Dressrosa
must find a way to make up their
one-minute difference before the
birdcage finishes contracting.